## **Brevin Tilmon**

My main skill set is developing algorithms and hardware for creating novel computer vision-based adaptive sensing systems. I have extensive lab experience interfacing and programming sensors such as machine vision cameras, MEMS mirrors, and depth sensors. Additionally, I have deep learning experience by collecting custom datasets and implementing models to enhance the previously mentioned sensors.

## **PERSONAL**

Phone (812) 568-3344 Mail btilmon@ufl.edu

Website https://btilmon.github.io/

## **EDUCATION**

### Ph.D. Electrical Engineering

2019-Present

University of Florida Advisor: Dr. Sanjeev Koppal

## B.S. Engineering Physics

2015-2019

Murray State University, 3.8/4.0

## **PUBLICATIONS**

- Brevin Tilmon, Eakta Jain, Silvia Ferrari, Sanjeev Koppal. "FoveaCam: A MEMS Mirror-Enabled Foveating Camera". ICCP 2020.
- Francesco Pittaluga, Zaid Tasneem, Justin Folden, Brevin Tilmon, Ayan Chakrabarti, Sanjeev Koppal. "A MEMS-Based Foveating LIDAR to Enable Real-Time Adaptive Depth Sensing". arXiv 2020.
- Kristofer Henderson, Xiaomeng Liu, Justin Folden, Brevin Tilmon, Suren Jayasuriya, Sanjeev Koppal. "Design and Calibration of a Fast Flying-Dot Projector for Dynamic Light Transport Acquisition". TCI 2020.
- Gheorge Bunget, Brevin Tilmon, Andrew Yee, Dylan Stewart, James Rogers, et al. "Novel Approach of Wavelet Analysis for Nonlinear Ultrasonic Measurements and Fatigue Assessment of Jet Engine Components". AIP 2018.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### • Graduate Research Assistant

2019-Present

Florida Optics and Computational Sensor Lab, University of Florida

 Design algorithms and hardware for adaptive imaging systems (cameras, lidars, projectors).

# • Undergraduate Research Intern Florida Optics and Computational Sensor Lab, University of Florida

2018

 Developed projector-camera system contributing to a publication in Transactions on Computational Imaging.

### • Undergraduate Research Assistant

2016-2019

Non Destructive Evaluations Lab, Murray State University

 Developed denoising wavelet algorithm in MATLAB that contributed to a publication in American Institute of Physics.

### • Electrical Engineering Intern

2017

Berry Global Inc.

Developed python application for real time control of production systems.

### • IEEE Robotics President

2017-2019

Murray State University IEEE Robotics Branch

 Competed in IEEE SoutheastCon Hardware(Robotics) Competition. Developed fully autonomous robots with team of classmates, placed top 20 percent in 2018 and 2019.

#### • Teaching Assistant

2016-2019

Murray State University

Instructed physics labs for electromagnetism and mechanics.

## **AWARDS**

NSF GRFP Honorable Mention 2020

Graduate School Preeminence Award, University of Florida

Sigma Pi Sigma, Murray State University

Jesse Jones Endowment, Murray State University

Engineering Physics Housing Scholarship, Murray State University

## **SKILLS**

**Programming:** C/C++, Python, MATLAB

Frameworks: OpenCV, PyTorch, Darknet, Tensorflow

Miscellaneous: Circuit design, Solidworks and 3D printing, Machine shop basics Graduate courses: Digital Signal Processing, Machine Learning, Adaptive Signal

Processing